[{"answer": "Yeah, this is for Alike", "docId": "Pariah.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "No she's the oldest one", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Who are you going with", "docId": "Pariah.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Oooh, I see. my friend, who are you going with", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "It was like seven of u", "docId": "Pariah.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Heeeell n", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Watch out, it's slippery", "docId": "Pariah.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I already told you what I think", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "It's supposed to fit like that", "docId": "Pariah.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I didn't have time for all of that. The brown ones were too big, anyway", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I'm tellin' that you got that thing", "docId": "Pariah.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I'm telling", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Sit still, people gon' think you got something", "docId": "Pariah.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "You not gon' take it off", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "This joint hurts, man. I'ma go take it off", "docId": "Pariah.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I'm gonna take it off", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "You not gon' take it off", "docId": "Pariah.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Where you gonna take it off at", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "What's the score", "docId": "Pariah.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "One", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " What i", "docId": "Pariah.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Say they like you, like you", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Go to your room", "docId": "Pariah.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I am not leaving you!", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": " `Member how we used t", "docId": "Pariah.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "that place's a long way awa", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "my frien", "docId": "Pariah.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "He told me, yes", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "You can always come back home", "docId": "Pariah.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I love you too", "qsentId": 30}]